And the ongoing launch in IV.
Thank you.
Next question.
Your next question comes from the line of James Quigley from Goldman Facts.
Please go ahead.
Hello, thank you for taking my second question.
So, you're just following up on the remoributinib food allergy data from the Phase 2 that is supporting the Phase 3 trial.
So, what is it in the modeling that you saw that makes the 75 milligram the most appropriate dose, given the data we've seen for the 100 milligram and the 25 milligram?
Is there a bridge between, where the efficacy is between the two, or would the 75 milligram dose have the same target engagement as 100 milligrams?
That's a great question.
So, we modeled this really carefully based on the full data set that we have.
And we do believe that at 75 milligrams we do have full target engagement and we should be able to achieve efficacy that approaches the 100 milligram dose.
But we've – and so, we felt like this was a reasonable approach to take.
Particularly, given that we want to move into should be the article feed.
We want to move into the adolescent population and FDA would surely ask us to use the minimum
required dose to achieve the efficacy required.
So, based on all our modeling, we believe we can get the necessary target engagement
at 75 milligrams and then deliver the efficacy that you saw in the study, which as you could
see was, you know, was really, you know, very compelling.
Next question.
Thank you.
We will now take our last question for today.
And the last question comes from the line of Steve Scaler from TD Securities.
Please go ahead.
Oh, thank you so much for the follow-up.
Slide 25 no longer mentions MFN, whereas the same slide in the Q4 deck did.
I'm just curious why.
I heard your earlier responses to Matthew's questions, but slide 25 suggests that Novartis
is increasingly confident in its ability to deal with MFN.
And I'm just wondering what has changed as we start 2021.
Slide 26.
Thank you.
Hold on.
One second, Steve.
We're just trying to get slide 25 up.
It's this.
Oh, okay.
So, I think no change in our perspective on MFN.
I mean, we've fully factored in MFN into the guidance that we've given, both for this
year and the five-year period.
So, that's fully factored in.
If anything, I think we've gotten even better now in modeling the MFN impact.
So, we've made clear assumptions.
We've made clear assumptions on the impact on the existing portfolio of medicines for
the Medicaid effect, as well as on future launches, a set of assumptions on launch phasing
for drugs that have a full MFN effect, and then we'll ultimately, of course, see how
this all unfolds.
We also have signed the agreements to allow us to not have an impact from tariffs with
the commercial agreement that we've signed with the U.S. government, as well as scaling
up, as you've seen, our manufacturing plants around the United States to allow us to produce
fully in the U.S. for the U.S., such that we wouldn't expect any tariff impact.
So, all that to say, I guess at this point, we feel confident enough with MFN that we don't
need to mention it anymore.
Hence, that's why you're not seeing it on the slides.
Thank you.
I think that is all the questions.
So, thank you all very, very much for an engaging discussion.
I know we have some follow-ups, but we'll get back to you.
We appreciate your time, as always, and we'll look forward to keeping you up-to-date in
the months ahead.
Have a great day.